Guide to the University Career Services, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Fellowship records, circa 1987-1988; Accession 1991-A-030
  - DAAD SCHOLARSHIPS:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - DOROT FOUNDATION TRAVEL GRANTS
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - EDITORIAL INTERNSHIPS (ASME, New York Times, Time Inc.):
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - ASME Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - ASME Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - ASME Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Time Inc. Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 113)
  - FULBRIGHT GRANTS:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - Sample Fulbright Committee Folder, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Campus Interview Info, Eval and Timetable, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Applications, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Notes Info Meeting/Committee Meeting, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Campus Rating Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Tic Sheets, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Applicants Forms 1 and 8, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Recommended/Not Recommended, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Winners, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Alternates, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Losers/Withdrawals, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - HEHRY FELLOWSHIP:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 141)
  - KEASBEY SCHOLARSHIPS:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - KODAK SCHOLARS PROGRAM:
    - Kodak Scholars Program, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 224)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 225)
  - LEADERSHIP AMERICA PROGRAM:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 226)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 227)
  - LUCE SCHOLARS PROGRAM:
    - Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 232)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 233)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 234)
  - MARSHALL SCHOLARSHIPS:
    - General Information, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 252)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 253)
  - MELLON FELLOWSHIPS IN THE HUMANITIES:
    - Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 254)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 255)
  - NCAA POSTGRADUATE SCHOLARSHIP PROGRAM:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 256)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 257)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 258)
  - NEW YORK TIMES EDITORIAL ASSISTANTSHIP:
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 260)
    - Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 261)
  - RHODES SCHOLARSHIPS:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - Rhodes and Marshall Applicants by Residential College, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 276)
  - SAINT ANDREW"S SOCIETY SCHOLSRSHIP PROGRAM:
    - Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 279)
  - HARRY S. TRUMAN SCHOLARSHIP PROGRAM:, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 285)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 286)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 287)
  - U.S.-U.S.S.R STUDENT EXCHANGE PROGRAM:
    - Basic Information, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 301)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 302)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 303)
  - YALE CLUB OF PRINCETON PRIZE:
    - Prize Forms, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 306)
    - Prize Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 307)
    - Prize Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 308)
  - YALE STUDIES IN THE ENVIRONMENT SUMMER INTERNSHIPS:
    - Information, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 323)
    - Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 324)
    - Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 325)
- Student records for the Class of 1987, Accession 1991-A-058
  - PREMED APPLICANTS
  - SPECIAL CATEGORY
  - PREMED APPLICANTS -- INACTIVE
  - SPEClAL CATEGORY
  - PREMED APPLICANTS - YELLOW CARDS ONLY
  - SPECIAL APPLICANTS - YELLOW CARDS ONLY
  - MEDICAL SCHOOLS APPLIED TO IN 1987 - LISTS (Box 3)
- Pre-medical student records for applicants to medical schools in 1988-1990, Accession 2001-A-077
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2065
  - Yellow registration cards -2bundles (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Yellow Registration cards (Box 4, Folder 372)
  - Yellow Registration Cards (Box 5, Folder 570)
- "A Guide to Post Graduate Planning", 1971; Accession 2004-A-107
  The materials are open for research.
  - "A Guide to Post Graduate Planning", 1971 (Box 1)
- Pre-medical student records, 1980-1996; Accession 2007-A-176
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2071
  - Walker, David Matthew, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1349)